{
    "id": "9255bb8002a14834bc2c8ea84b61abb2",
    "title": "Subordinating Conjunctions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The children were happy ………………….. the show began.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "when",
                "as",
                "while"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6655cef19db74386b2ef9b179fdc3f43"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the place …………………. the accident occurred.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "there",
                "when",
                "where"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "72424f520e314decb028bba8340bf31c"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………. he worked hard, he couldn’t win the first prize.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Though",
                "Despite",
                "However"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e089ad7270fd49339983abf7f26830f7"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will go ………………… he forbids me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "even if",
                "even as"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2b06d11f34694c6c9793b1fcffdf6997"
        },
        {
            "question": "She will not come ………………….. you invite her.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "unless",
                "whether"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "29628005c2f94809a47f2de8ea8ce191"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………. she is pretty, I don’t like her.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Though",
                "As",
                "Even if"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8657b9c3962a42d3a31e8de008c74a5b"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is surprising …………………. she didn’t invite you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "that",
                "what"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3689a9797cd4459da944dcddbe923085"
        },
        {
            "question": "Will you wait here ………………… I come?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "unless",
                "until"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "cc0391f063454b13af39a51f23227fb1"
        },
        {
            "question": "I couldn’t go ………………….. it was raining.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "though",
                "because",
                "hence"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c8ba6113969546e2a129b1514205db56"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………….. the sky is overcast we will cancel the picnic.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Since",
                "That",
                "Whether"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a6b3c6a8c2a14528a541fb7c40e07c2d"
        },
        {
            "question": "They say a silent prayer ………………. they start the class.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "before",
                "because"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7872f70d333144b8b6d165d0326c36d0"
        },
        {
            "question": "Do ………………… you have been directed.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "as",
                "what"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a7daf2927a4d4802879f4f1c2f81b11d"
        }
    ]
}